Cesar Celis Hernandez

Software Engineer

Profile

Passionate software engineer with 7+ years of experience and great ambition to keep learning. Strong knowledge with Python for automation and development of any imaginable idea. Highly Focused, capable of self-learning and excellent team worker.

Employment History

Web Developer at Givex, Toronto

August 2019 — Present

- Developed new web features for gift cards and loyalty programs.
- Performed maintenance of complex code to support new changes.
- Implemented PostgreSQL queries to provide accurate data in our API

QA Engineer at Espressive, Guadalajara

June 2017 — July 2019

- Designed a plan to validate proper answers of a Virtual Support Agent.
- Created Test Cases for scenarios we supported in the Virtual Agent.
- Developed Python/Selenium framework for test automation.
- Worked well independently and on a team to solve problems.

Validation Engineer at Intel, Guadalajara

April 2012 — May 2017

- · Created bash scripts to perform automation for testing
- Found HW issues that got corrected to prevent silicon recall
- · Performed HW testing for different intel platforms at Graphic Interface
- Served as a friendly, hardworking, and punctual employee.

Education

B.S. Information Technology, Instituto Tecnológico y de Estudios Superiores de Monterrey (ITESM), Guadalajara

August 2005 — December 2011

• Educational Credential Assessment from University of Toronto.

Courses

Using Python for Automation, LinkedIn

September 2020 — September 2020

Time Management Fundamentals, LinkedIn

September 2020 — September 2020

Details

4168278578

celis.hernandez.cesar@gmail.com

Links

LinkedIn GitHub

Hackerrank

Skills

Docker

Git

jQuery

HTML

Python

SQL

Django

CSS

JavaScript

Selenium

Languages

English

Spanish